<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv generator-info-name="WebGrab+Plus/w MDB &amp; REX Postprocess -- version V3.2.2.0 -- Jan van Straaten" generator-info-url="http://www.webgrabplus.com">

<channel id="AS100">
	<display-name lang="en">AS100</display-name>
    <url>http://www.astro.com.my</url>
</channel>
<channel id="AS400">
	<display-name lang="en">AS400</display-name>
    <url>http://www.astro.com.my</url>
</channel>
<channel id="AS795">
	<display-name lang="en">AS795</display-name>
    <url>http://www.astro.com.my</url>
</channel>
<channel id="AS796">
	<display-name lang="en">AS796</display-name>
    <url>http://www.astro.com.my</url>
</channel>
<channel id="AS797">
	<display-name lang="en">AS797</display-name>
    <url>http://www.astro.com.my</url>
</channel>
<channel id="AS809">
	<display-name lang="en">AS809</display-name>
    <url>http://www.astro.com.my</url>
</channel>
<channel id="AS809">
	<display-name lang="en">AS809</display-name>
    <url>http://www.astro.com.my</url>
</channel>
<channel id="AS825">
	<display-name lang="en">AS825</display-name>
    <url>http://www.astro.com.my</url>
</channel>
<programme start="20230921000000 +0800" stop="20230921003000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP09 Standing Tall for Someone Special 誰がための勇姿, Taga Tame no Yūshi)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Kanata meets a young girl, Mika. She says she wants Kanata/Ultraman Decker to fight her father?! Her father is the Space Martial Arts Champion, Grace... Will the duel between Decker and Grace take place? And how will it end?!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921003000 +0800" stop="20230921010000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP10 Man and Monster 人と怪獣, Hito to Kaijū)</title>
    <desc lang="en">The mysterious monster Neomegas appears suddenly in town, defeats several other monsters, and leaves. Vice-Captain Kaizaki tries to find out what's really going out, when she remembers the words of her mentor. The terrifying true meaning behind those words reveals itself before Kanata, the GUTS-Select team, and Ultraman Decker!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921010000 +0800" stop="20230921021500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Taiga The Movie (New Generation Climax)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Hiroyuki Kudo, working at the private security organization EGIS, has the power to transform into three Ultra Heroes: Taiga, Titas, and Fuma. Battling and defeating many enemies together, the bond between Hiroyuki and Taiga has deepened. However, someone has been targeting Hiroyuki. Noticing this, the New Generation Heroes come together to save him. Hikaru, Sho, Daichi, Gai, Riku, Katsumi, Isami, and even Taiga’s father Ultraman Taro have all come down to Earth. However, Ultraman Taro violently attacks his son Taiga. What happened to Taro? Will Taiga be able to fight against his father!? The New Generation Heroes now stand together to confront a bigger, darker power!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://news.ultramanconnection.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/62d70fd3cc456dc40514dcec_ULTRAMAN-TAIGA-NEXT-FEATURE-FILM-TO-HIT-THEATERS-IN-JAPAN.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921021500 +0800" stop="20230921024000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Trigger: New Generation Tiga (Ep16)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Today, GUTS-Select team was formed while Martian settlement Kengo Manaka lived his life as a botanist. Kengo has a fated encounter the giant of light from the past, and his name is Ultraman Trigger.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/ultra/images/b/bb/TriggerTitleCard.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20210617110145" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921024000 +0800" stop="20230921030500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Trigger: New Generation Tiga (Ep17)</title>
    <desc lang="en">A new monster, Metsu-Orochi, comes out of the body of Metsu-Orga and absorbs energy of all kinds! To defeat this huge monster even more powerful than Metsu-Orga, GUTS-Select put their plans to action. Right in the thick of things, Trigger Dark appears again!

Kengo and the team do all they can to survive this crisis!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/ultra/images/b/bb/TriggerTitleCard.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20210617110145" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921030500 +0800" stop="20230921033000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Trigger: New Generation Tiga (Ep18)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Captain Tatsumi is promoted to Lead Commander of GUTS-Select Asia! While Kengo and crew plan a surprise celebration, the other members all experience incredibly good luck as well?! What a perfect day... or so they think until the monster Golba appears. Can the team safely pull off their surprise celebration?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/ultra/images/b/bb/TriggerTitleCard.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20210617110145" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921033000 +0800" stop="20230921035500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Trigger: New Generation Tiga (Ep19)</title>
    <desc lang="en">An unidentified cosmic wave known as “Morpheus R” reacts to minds filled with desire. It causes the Dark Giants to begin fighting among themselves! As they lay waste to the city, a mysterious man is following Yuna… When the dark being tests Yuna’s resolve, a miraculous Light descends!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/ultra/images/b/bb/TriggerTitleCard.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20210617110145" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921035500 +0800" stop="20230921042000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Trigger: New Generation Tiga (Ep20)</title>
    <desc lang="en">As Yuna awakens to Yuzare’s power, the blue Monster God Barriguiler descends from space! It seems to have some connection to Yuzare in the ancient past, but just what does it want?! And watch out, Yuna’s in danger! Can Kengo and Akito come to Yuna’s rescue in time?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/ultra/images/b/bb/TriggerTitleCard.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20210617110145" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921042000 +0800" stop="20230921044500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Trigger: New Generation Tiga (EP21)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Today, GUTS-Select team was formed while Martian settlement Kengo Manaka lived his life as a botanist. Kengo has a fated encounter the giant of light from the past, and his name is Ultraman Trigger.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/ultra/images/b/bb/TriggerTitleCard.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20210617110145" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921044500 +0800" stop="20230921060000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Taiga The Movie (New Generation Climax)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Hiroyuki Kudo, working at the private security organization EGIS, has the power to transform into three Ultra Heroes: Taiga, Titas, and Fuma. Battling and defeating many enemies together, the bond between Hiroyuki and Taiga has deepened. However, someone has been targeting Hiroyuki. Noticing this, the New Generation Heroes come together to save him. Hikaru, Sho, Daichi, Gai, Riku, Katsumi, Isami, and even Taiga’s father Ultraman Taro have all come down to Earth. However, Ultraman Taro violently attacks his son Taiga. What happened to Taro? Will Taiga be able to fight against his father!? The New Generation Heroes now stand together to confront a bigger, darker power!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://news.ultramanconnection.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/62d70fd3cc456dc40514dcec_ULTRAMAN-TAIGA-NEXT-FEATURE-FILM-TO-HIT-THEATERS-IN-JAPAN.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921060000 +0800" stop="20230921063000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Blazar (EP05 The Mountain Roars 山が吠える, Yama ga Hoeru)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Practice runs for the new railgun, Mega Shot, is conducted in Anri's hometown. That's where Anri has an unexpected reunion with her childhood friend, Mizuho. Mizuho begs for them to cancel the practice runs. She insists that the removal of the shrine for the installation of the Mega Shot will awaken Dorgo, the local guardian god, but Anri finds it hard to believe. However, during the practice there's a big earth tremor...</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_KIFXH_IVP_LAND_672x378_2023616_151457.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921063000 +0800" stop="20230921070000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Blazar (EP06 The Invading Aurora 侵略のオーロラ, Shinryaku no Ōrora)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Yasunobu was rambling about his day to Cururu, a washer at the laundromat, when Alien Cannan Herbie suddenly appears before him. Herbie uses the Aurora Beam to manipulate machines and this was the reason for the increasing car and airplane accidents around the world. And that's not the end of it: it turns out that Earth Garon had also been shot with the Aurora Beam! What will Yasunobu do?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_KIFXH_IVP_LAND_672x378_2023616_151457.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921070000 +0800" stop="20230921073000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Blazar (EP07 Rainbow Appears: Part 1 虹が出た（前編）, Niji ga Deta (Zenpen))</title>
    <desc lang="en">Upside-down rainbows are being sighted throughout Japan. They are said to herald the onset of rain. Gento suspects that a kaiju may be behind this and decides to visit Professor Yokomine, a leading kaijuologist and also his mentor from school. Yokomine tells him about Nijikagachi, a god-like being that can at times bless the land with rain and at times summon utter destruction. That's when Gento receives news about an appearance of a giant kaiju!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_KIFXH_IVP_LAND_672x378_2023616_151457.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921073000 +0800" stop="20230921080000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Blazar (EP08 Rainbow Appears: Part 2 虹が出た（後編）, Niji ga deta (Kōhen))</title>
    <desc lang="en">The typhoons that Nijikagachi created are about to wash away civilization. Gento decides to deploy Earth Garon's new Mod.2 unit into battle to defeat Nijikagachi. Teruaki, who had a deep respect for Yokomine, goes to persuade the mastermind of the plot.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_KIFXH_IVP_LAND_672x378_2023616_151457.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921080000 +0800" stop="20230921083000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Blazar (EP09 Planet of Music オトノホシ, Otonohoshi)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Anri receives a letter. It contained a concert ticket for a band led by Hoichi Tsukushi, someone that Anri had gotten to know through music. That's when the robot kaiju Garamon appears from a meteorite that came from outer space. Anri realizes that Garamon's behavior is controlled by a mysterious sound wave, and she has a hunch...</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_KIFXH_IVP_LAND_672x378_2023616_151457.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921083000 +0800" stop="20230921090000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP11 Machine God Deployed 機神出撃, Kishin Shutsugeki)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Finally! Finally!! GUTS-Select are given with new equipment in the form of a robot! It's name is the "Terraphaser"!! Everyone is excited to meet the robot they'd been waiting for, but for some reason monsters appear every time they try to test a boot-up sequence!! As Ultraman Decker holds off the monsters, can the team safely start-up the Terraphaser?!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921090000 +0800" stop="20230921093000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP12 Neomegas Strikes Back ネオメガスの逆襲, Neomegasu no Gyakushū)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Sphere-Neomegas is born from the remaining Neomegas cells. Ultraman Decker and GUTS-Select are forced to fight against its overwhelming power. Kanata and his team are devastated by their inability to accomplish anything, but they encourage each other and begin a counterattack operation, mobilizing all their strength with Terraphaser at the center!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921093000 +0800" stop="20230921100000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP13 Jumble Rock ジャンブル・ロック, Janburu Rokku)</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Nursedessei's systems suddenly go down. A power-outage?! Who appears in this emergency but Marluru of the previous GUTS-Select team! Kanata and the crew are grateful for their seniors' timely appearance, but Marluru's sharp tongue leads to heated outbursts! Will Kanata and crew figure out how to work with Marluru and safely restore power to the Nursedessei?!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921100000 +0800" stop="20230921103000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP14 Birth of a Dark God 魔神誕生, Majin Tanjō)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ultraman Decker and the Terraphaser prove to be the ultimate duo! Kanata is overjoyed when the pair's successive victories increase their popularity around the world. Suddenly, the Spheresaurus appears again at the spaceport! It seems to be even stronger than last time. As the ultimate duo faces against the monster, a disturbing shadow begins to move...</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921103000 +0800" stop="20230921110000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP15 A Promise for Tomorrow 明日への約束, Ashita e no Yakusoku)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Kanata and the crew of GUTS-Select are shaken by an unforeseen event... Just who is the mysterious figure that appears before Kanata?! When the true face behind the Sphere and the truth about Ultraman Decker are revealed, a dynamic miracle form appears!!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921110000 +0800" stop="20230921113000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP16 Stay As You Are 君は君のままで, Kimi wa Kimi no mama de)</title>
    <desc lang="en"> "Humanity must not venture into space..." Kanata and the others struggle to take in those words, but just then the small monster Spinnie appears, and a TPU all-member operation begins to capture it. After all of their plans to capture it fail and Spinnie makes fun of him, Kanata vents by saying something horrible to Ryuumon...</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921113000 +0800" stop="20230921120000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP17 Investigation from the Past 過去よりの調べ, Kako yori no Shirabe)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Captian Murahoshi is under investigation?! The Director of the TPU's Internal Affairs, Agent Nigel, suspects Captain and Agams might be working together. Kanata is shocked, but Nigel shows no mercy and looks for any suspicious acitivity from Murahoshi. Why doesn't Nigel trust Murahoshi? Is there any way to clear Captain's name?!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921120000 +0800" stop="20230921135000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultra Galaxy Fight: The Absolute Conspiracy</title>
    <desc lang="en">Together with Ultraman Max, Ultraman Ribut senses a strange presence on a certain planet... However, it's a trap set by an enemy seeking revenge.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/ultra/images/3/3b/UGFTACTitle.png/revision/latest?cb=20211213041138" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921135000 +0800" stop="20230921142000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Zero: The Chronicle (EP14)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ultraman Mebius Battle File (ウルトラマンメビウスバトルファイル, Urutoraman Mebiusu Batoru Fairu): The only episode to not be largely re-used from the two Ultraman Retsuden seasons, this episode showcases Ultraman Mebius Gaiden: Ghost Rebirth. In newly-recorded footage, Rei makes a brief appearance at the end.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E95_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_17255.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921142000 +0800" stop="20230921145000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Zero: The Chronicle (EP15)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Mega Monster Battle: Ultra Galaxy Legends - Chapter 1: The Rebellion of Belial (大怪獣バトル ウルトラ銀河伝説 「第１章　反逆のベリアル」, Daikaijū Batoru Urutora Ginga Densetsu - Dai Ichi Shō: Hangyaku no Beriaru)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E95_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_17255.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921145000 +0800" stop="20230921152000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Zero: The Chronicle (EP16)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Mega Monster Battle: Ultra Galaxy Legends - Chapter 2: Rei and Mebius (大怪獣バトル ウルトラ銀河伝説 「第２章　レイとメビウス」, Daikaijū Batoru Urutora Ginga Densetsu - Dai Ni Shō: Rei to Mebiusu)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E95_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_17255.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921152000 +0800" stop="20230921155000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Zero: The Chronicle (EP18)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Mega Monster Battle: Ultra Galaxy Legends - Chapter 4: Ultraman Zero Arrives (大怪獣バトル ウルトラ銀河伝説 「第４章　ウルトラマンゼロ参上」, Daikaijū Batoru Urutora Ginga Densetsu - Dai Yon Shō: Urutoraman Zero Sanjō)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E95_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_17255.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921155000 +0800" stop="20230921162000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Zero: The Chronicle (EP19)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Mega Monster Battle: Ultra Galaxy Legends - Final Chapter: Restore the Light of the Galaxy (大怪獣バトル ウルトラ銀河伝説 「最終章　よみがえれ銀河の光」, Daikaijū Batoru Urutora Ginga Densetsu - Saishū Shō: Yomigaere Ginga no Hikari)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E95_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_17255.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921162000 +0800" stop="20230921165000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Zero: The Chronicle (EP20)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Killer The Beatstar - Part 1: The Steel Army (キラー ザ ビートスター パート①「鋼鉄の軍団」, Kirā Za Bītosutā Pāto Wan - Kōtetsu no Gundan)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E95_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_17255.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921165000 +0800" stop="20230921172000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Zero: The Chronicle (EP21)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Killer The Beatstar - Part 2: The Steel Dictator (キラー ザ ビートスター パート②「鋼の独裁者」, Kirā Za Bītosutā Pāto Tsu - Hagane no Dokusai-sha)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E95_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_17255.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921172000 +0800" stop="20230921175000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Zero: The Chronicle (EP23)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ultraman Zero - Hero Retsuden (ウルトラマンゼロ 英雄列伝, Urutoraman Zero Eiyū Retsuden): The same as episode 79 of Ultraman Retsuden, this episode highlights clips from multiple Zero movies and specials</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E95_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_17255.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921175000 +0800" stop="20230921182000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Blazar (EP05 The Mountain Roars 山が吠える, Yama ga Hoeru)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Practice runs for the new railgun, Mega Shot, is conducted in Anri's hometown. That's where Anri has an unexpected reunion with her childhood friend, Mizuho. Mizuho begs for them to cancel the practice runs. She insists that the removal of the shrine for the installation of the Mega Shot will awaken Dorgo, the local guardian god, but Anri finds it hard to believe. However, during the practice there's a big earth tremor...</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_KIFXH_IVP_LAND_672x378_2023616_151457.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921182000 +0800" stop="20230921185000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Blazar (EP06 The Invading Aurora 侵略のオーロラ, Shinryaku no Ōrora)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Yasunobu was rambling about his day to Cururu, a washer at the laundromat, when Alien Cannan Herbie suddenly appears before him. Herbie uses the Aurora Beam to manipulate machines and this was the reason for the increasing car and airplane accidents around the world. And that's not the end of it: it turns out that Earth Garon had also been shot with the Aurora Beam! What will Yasunobu do?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_KIFXH_IVP_LAND_672x378_2023616_151457.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921185000 +0800" stop="20230921192000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Blazar (EP07 Rainbow Appears: Part 1 虹が出た（前編）, Niji ga Deta (Zenpen))</title>
    <desc lang="en">Upside-down rainbows are being sighted throughout Japan. They are said to herald the onset of rain. Gento suspects that a kaiju may be behind this and decides to visit Professor Yokomine, a leading kaijuologist and also his mentor from school. Yokomine tells him about Nijikagachi, a god-like being that can at times bless the land with rain and at times summon utter destruction. That's when Gento receives news about an appearance of a giant kaiju!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_KIFXH_IVP_LAND_672x378_2023616_151457.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921192000 +0800" stop="20230921195000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Blazar (EP08 Rainbow Appears: Part 2 虹が出た（後編）, Niji ga deta (Kōhen))</title>
    <desc lang="en">The typhoons that Nijikagachi created are about to wash away civilization. Gento decides to deploy Earth Garon's new Mod.2 unit into battle to defeat Nijikagachi. Teruaki, who had a deep respect for Yokomine, goes to persuade the mastermind of the plot.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_KIFXH_IVP_LAND_672x378_2023616_151457.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921195000 +0800" stop="20230921202000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Blazar (EP09 Planet of Music オトノホシ, Otonohoshi)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Anri receives a letter. It contained a concert ticket for a band led by Hoichi Tsukushi, someone that Anri had gotten to know through music. That's when the robot kaiju Garamon appears from a meteorite that came from outer space. Anri realizes that Garamon's behavior is controlled by a mysterious sound wave, and she has a hunch...</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_KIFXH_IVP_LAND_672x378_2023616_151457.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921202000 +0800" stop="20230921205000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Blazar (EP10 Parent and Child 親と子, Oya to Ko)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Gento's son, Jun, wants to go see a newly discovered egg shown on television, so the Hiruma family decide to go on a day trip to visit it. There, they witness the birth of Baby Demaaga. In the midst of the capture operation led by the GGF, the mother Demaaga makes an appearance. The GGF launches attacks as the parent kaiju approaches its baby. While evacuating, Gento can't help but feel mixed emotions seeing Demaaga trying to protect its child. Suddenly, the Blazar Brace appears on Gento's left arm.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_KIFXH_IVP_LAND_672x378_2023616_151457.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921205000 +0800" stop="20230921230000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultra Galaxy Fight (The Destined Crossroad)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ultra Galaxy Fight: The Destined Crossroad is the third installment of the Ultra Galaxy Fight series, continued from the previous series Ultra Galaxy Fight: The Absolute Conspiracy which had a shocking ending. Ultra Heroes vs Absolutian, the destined battle is about to reshape the galaxy!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://news.ultramanconnection.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/62d70a2898f17d6b9a8422a6_ULTRA-GALAXY-FIGHT_-THE-DESTINED-CROSSROAD-TO-PREMIERE-ON-ULTRAMAN-CONNECTION.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921230000 +0800" stop="20230921233000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP11 Machine God Deployed 機神出撃, Kishin Shutsugeki)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Finally! Finally!! GUTS-Select are given with new equipment in the form of a robot! It's name is the "Terraphaser"!! Everyone is excited to meet the robot they'd been waiting for, but for some reason monsters appear every time they try to test a boot-up sequence!! As Ultraman Decker holds off the monsters, can the team safely start-up the Terraphaser?!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921233000 +0800" stop="20230922000000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP12 Neomegas Strikes Back ネオメガスの逆襲, Neomegasu no Gyakushū)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Sphere-Neomegas is born from the remaining Neomegas cells. Ultraman Decker and GUTS-Select are forced to fight against its overwhelming power. Kanata and his team are devastated by their inability to accomplish anything, but they encourage each other and begin a counterattack operation, mobilizing all their strength with Terraphaser at the center!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922000000 +0800" stop="20230922003000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP13 Jumble Rock ジャンブル・ロック, Janburu Rokku)</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Nursedessei's systems suddenly go down. A power-outage?! Who appears in this emergency but Marluru of the previous GUTS-Select team! Kanata and the crew are grateful for their seniors' timely appearance, but Marluru's sharp tongue leads to heated outbursts! Will Kanata and crew figure out how to work with Marluru and safely restore power to the Nursedessei?!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922003000 +0800" stop="20230922010000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP14 Birth of a Dark God 魔神誕生, Majin Tanjō)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ultraman Decker and the Terraphaser prove to be the ultimate duo! Kanata is overjoyed when the pair's successive victories increase their popularity around the world. Suddenly, the Spheresaurus appears again at the spaceport! It seems to be even stronger than last time. As the ultimate duo faces against the monster, a disturbing shadow begins to move...</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922010000 +0800" stop="20230922025000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultra Galaxy Fight: The Absolute Conspiracy</title>
    <desc lang="en">Together with Ultraman Max, Ultraman Ribut senses a strange presence on a certain planet... However, it's a trap set by an enemy seeking revenge.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/ultra/images/3/3b/UGFTACTitle.png/revision/latest?cb=20211213041138" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922025000 +0800" stop="20230922031500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP15 A Promise for Tomorrow 明日への約束, Ashita e no Yakusoku)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Kanata and the crew of GUTS-Select are shaken by an unforeseen event... Just who is the mysterious figure that appears before Kanata?! When the true face behind the Sphere and the truth about Ultraman Decker are revealed, a dynamic miracle form appears!!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922031500 +0800" stop="20230922034000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP16 Stay As You Are 君は君のままで, Kimi wa Kimi no mama de)</title>
    <desc lang="en"> "Humanity must not venture into space..." Kanata and the others struggle to take in those words, but just then the small monster Spinnie appears, and a TPU all-member operation begins to capture it. After all of their plans to capture it fail and Spinnie makes fun of him, Kanata vents by saying something horrible to Ryuumon...</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922034000 +0800" stop="20230922041000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP17 Investigation from the Past 過去よりの調べ, Kako yori no Shirabe)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Captian Murahoshi is under investigation?! The Director of the TPU's Internal Affairs, Agent Nigel, suspects Captain and Agams might be working together. Kanata is shocked, but Nigel shows no mercy and looks for any suspicious acitivity from Murahoshi. Why doesn't Nigel trust Murahoshi? Is there any way to clear Captain's name?!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922041000 +0800" stop="20230922060000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultra Galaxy Fight: The Absolute Conspiracy</title>
    <desc lang="en">Together with Ultraman Max, Ultraman Ribut senses a strange presence on a certain planet... However, it's a trap set by an enemy seeking revenge.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/ultra/images/3/3b/UGFTACTitle.png/revision/latest?cb=20211213041138" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922060000 +0800" stop="20230922063000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Zero: The Chronicle (EP23)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ultraman Zero - Hero Retsuden (ウルトラマンゼロ 英雄列伝, Urutoraman Zero Eiyū Retsuden): The same as episode 79 of Ultraman Retsuden, this episode highlights clips from multiple Zero movies and specials</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E95_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_17255.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922063000 +0800" stop="20230922070000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Zero: The Chronicle (EP24)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ultra Zero Fight - Shining Zero (Part 1) (ウルトラゼロファイト 輝きのゼロ（前編）, Urutora Zero Faito Kagayaki no Zero (Zenpen))</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E95_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_17255.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922070000 +0800" stop="20230922073000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Zero: The Chronicle (EP25)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ultra Zero Fight - Shining Zero (Part 2) (ウルトラゼロファイト 輝きのゼロ（後編）, Urutora Zero Faito Kagayaki no Zero (Kōhen))</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E95_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_17255.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922073000 +0800" stop="20230922080000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Zero: The Chronicle (EP26)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ultraman Zero! Determination of a New Battle!! (ウルトラマンゼロ! 新たな戦いへの決意!!, Urutoraman Zero! Aratana Tatakai e no Ketsui!!): The final episode of Ultraman Retsuden, recapping the second part of Ultra Zero Fight.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://resizer-acm.eco.astro.com.my/tr:w-800/https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E95_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_17255.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922080000 +0800" stop="20230922083000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Zero: The Chronicle (EP01)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ultraman Zero VS Darklops Zero - Part 1: Multidimensional Threat! (ウルトラマンゼロVSダークロプスゼロ パート①「多次元の脅威！」, Urutoraman Zero VS Dākuropusu Zero Pāto Wan - Tajigen no Kyōi!)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://resizer-acm.eco.astro.com.my/tr:w-800/https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E95_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_17255.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922083000 +0800" stop="20230922090000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Z (EP10. Here Comes the Space Pirate! 宇宙海賊登場, Uchū Kaizoku Tōjō)</title>
    <desc lang="en">The space pirate, Alien Barossa sneaks into STORAGE to retrieve King Joe! This space pirate is known for using various robbed tools and weapons from space and is a powerful enemy! In addition, King Joe is about to move again! Can Haruki stop this pirate?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E96_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_171625.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922090000 +0800" stop="20230922093000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Z (EP11. What Must Be Defended, 守るべきもの, Mamorubeki mono)</title>
    <desc lang="en">SSA-3 King Joe STORAGE Custom is finally complete! With weapons equipped to every inch of its body, this super robot wields tremendous power. Meanwhile, Red King appears before STORAGE. It seems, however, that this Red King has a secret...</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E96_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_171625.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922093000 +0800" stop="20230922100000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Z (EP12. The Cry of Life, 叫ぶ命, Sakebu Inochi)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ten years ago, a monster crashed to Earth and fell into a deep sleep. Now that monster, Grigio Raiden, has awakened! Z faces off against the monster, but something is wrong with Haruki... King Joe STORAGE Custom fights hard to follow the lackluster Z. How will this battle end?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E96_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_171625.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922100000 +0800" stop="20230922103000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Z (EP13. I'll Feast on Medals!, メダルいただきます!, Medaru Itadakimasu!)</title>
    <desc lang="en">With the sudden appearance of the Four-Dimensional Monster Bullton, the STORAGE base is thrown into chaos! Time and space become warped and twisted, transforming the STORAGE base into a dimensional prison. Meanwhile, Haruki is confronted with a mysterious phenomenon!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E96_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_171625.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922103000 +0800" stop="20230922110000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Z (EP14. Four-Dimensional Capriccio, 四次元狂騒曲, Yojigen Kyōsō-kyoku)</title>
    <desc lang="en">The space pirate, Alien Barossa sneaks into STORAGE to retrieve King Joe! This space pirate is known for using various robbed tools and weapons from space and is a powerful enemy! In addition, King Joe is about to move again! Can Haruki stop this pirate?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E96_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_171625.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922110000 +0800" stop="20230922113000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Z (EP15. A Warrior's Duty, 戦士の使命, Senshi no Shimei)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Emergency contact from Ultraman Geed! It seems that a distortion is created in the universe, and a void monster, Greeza, who returns everything to nothing, appears. We need new power to face this threat! Yes, the strongest figure of Ultraman Z is born here now!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E96_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_171625.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922113000 +0800" stop="20230922120000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Z (EP16. The Lion's Cry 獅子の声, Shishi no Koe)</title>
    <desc lang="en">The day has come for Horoboros, a monster that Yuka saw as a child, to awaken from its long slumber! The key to appeasing the raging Horoboros lies in a mysterious word recorded in an ancient document. Yuka sets out to decipher this writing, but Kaburagi's dark power is reaching out to Horoboros...!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E96_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_171625.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922120000 +0800" stop="20230922141000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultra Galaxy Fight (The Destined Crossroad)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ultra Galaxy Fight: The Destined Crossroad is the third installment of the Ultra Galaxy Fight series, continued from the previous series Ultra Galaxy Fight: The Absolute Conspiracy which had a shocking ending. Ultra Heroes vs Absolutian, the destined battle is about to reshape the galaxy!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://news.ultramanconnection.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/62d70a2898f17d6b9a8422a6_ULTRA-GALAXY-FIGHT_-THE-DESTINED-CROSSROAD-TO-PREMIERE-ON-ULTRAMAN-CONNECTION.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922141000 +0800" stop="20230922144000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Trigger: New Generation Tiga (Ep24)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Today, GUTS-Select team was formed while Martian settlement Kengo Manaka lived his life as a botanist. Kengo has a fated encounter the giant of light from the past, and his name is Ultraman Trigger.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/ultra/images/b/bb/TriggerTitleCard.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20210617110145" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922144000 +0800" stop="20230922151000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Trigger: New Generation Tiga (Ep25)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Today, GUTS-Select team was formed while Martian settlement Kengo Manaka lived his life as a botanist. Kengo has a fated encounter the giant of light from the past, and his name is Ultraman Trigger.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/ultra/images/b/bb/TriggerTitleCard.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20210617110145" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922151000 +0800" stop="20230922154000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Trigger: New Generation Tiga (Ep01)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Today, GUTS-Select team was formed while Martian settlement Kengo Manaka lived his life as a botanist. Kengo has a fated encounter the giant of light from the past, and his name is Ultraman Trigger.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/ultra/images/b/bb/TriggerTitleCard.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20210617110145" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922154000 +0800" stop="20230922161000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Trigger: New Generation Tiga (Ep02)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Today, GUTS-Select team was formed while Martian settlement Kengo Manaka lived his life as a botanist. Kengo has a fated encounter the giant of light from the past, and his name is Ultraman Trigger.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/ultra/images/b/bb/TriggerTitleCard.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20210617110145" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922161000 +0800" stop="20230922164000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Trigger: New Generation Tiga (Ep03)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Today, GUTS-Select team was formed while Martian settlement Kengo Manaka lived his life as a botanist. Kengo has a fated encounter the giant of light from the past, and his name is Ultraman Trigger.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/ultra/images/b/bb/TriggerTitleCard.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20210617110145" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922164000 +0800" stop="20230922171000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Trigger: New Generation Tiga (Ep04)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Today, GUTS-Select team was formed while Martian settlement Kengo Manaka lived his life as a botanist. Kengo has a fated encounter the giant of light from the past, and his name is Ultraman Trigger.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/ultra/images/b/bb/TriggerTitleCard.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20210617110145" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922171000 +0800" stop="20230922174000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Zero: The Chronicle (EP23)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ultraman Zero - Hero Retsuden (ウルトラマンゼロ 英雄列伝, Urutoraman Zero Eiyū Retsuden): The same as episode 79 of Ultraman Retsuden, this episode highlights clips from multiple Zero movies and specials</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E95_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_17255.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922174000 +0800" stop="20230922181000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Zero: The Chronicle (EP24)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ultra Zero Fight - Shining Zero (Part 1) (ウルトラゼロファイト 輝きのゼロ（前編）, Urutora Zero Faito Kagayaki no Zero (Zenpen))</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E95_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_17255.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922181000 +0800" stop="20230922184000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Zero: The Chronicle (EP25)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ultra Zero Fight - Shining Zero (Part 2) (ウルトラゼロファイト 輝きのゼロ（後編）, Urutora Zero Faito Kagayaki no Zero (Kōhen))</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E95_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_17255.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922184000 +0800" stop="20230922191000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Zero: The Chronicle (EP26)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ultraman Zero! Determination of a New Battle!! (ウルトラマンゼロ! 新たな戦いへの決意!!, Urutoraman Zero! Aratana Tatakai e no Ketsui!!): The final episode of Ultraman Retsuden, recapping the second part of Ultra Zero Fight.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://resizer-acm.eco.astro.com.my/tr:w-800/https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E95_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_17255.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922191000 +0800" stop="20230922194000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Zero: The Chronicle (EP01)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ultraman Zero VS Darklops Zero - Part 1: Multidimensional Threat! (ウルトラマンゼロVSダークロプスゼロ パート①「多次元の脅威！」, Urutoraman Zero VS Dākuropusu Zero Pāto Wan - Tajigen no Kyōi!)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://resizer-acm.eco.astro.com.my/tr:w-800/https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E95_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_17255.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922194000 +0800" stop="20230922201000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Zero: The Chronicle (EP23)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ultraman Zero - Hero Retsuden (ウルトラマンゼロ 英雄列伝, Urutoraman Zero Eiyū Retsuden): The same as episode 79 of Ultraman Retsuden, this episode highlights clips from multiple Zero movies and specials</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E95_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_17255.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922201000 +0800" stop="20230922204000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Zero: The Chronicle (EP24)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ultra Zero Fight - Shining Zero (Part 1) (ウルトラゼロファイト 輝きのゼロ（前編）, Urutora Zero Faito Kagayaki no Zero (Zenpen))</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E95_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_17255.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922204000 +0800" stop="20230922223500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultra Galaxy Fight: The Absolute Conspiracy</title>
    <desc lang="en">Together with Ultraman Max, Ultraman Ribut senses a strange presence on a certain planet... However, it's a trap set by an enemy seeking revenge.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/ultra/images/3/3b/UGFTACTitle.png/revision/latest?cb=20211213041138" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922223500 +0800" stop="20230922230000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Z (EP10. Here Comes the Space Pirate! 宇宙海賊登場, Uchū Kaizoku Tōjō)</title>
    <desc lang="en">The space pirate, Alien Barossa sneaks into STORAGE to retrieve King Joe! This space pirate is known for using various robbed tools and weapons from space and is a powerful enemy! In addition, King Joe is about to move again! Can Haruki stop this pirate?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E96_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_171625.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922230000 +0800" stop="20230922233000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Z (EP11. What Must Be Defended, 守るべきもの, Mamorubeki mono)</title>
    <desc lang="en">SSA-3 King Joe STORAGE Custom is finally complete! With weapons equipped to every inch of its body, this super robot wields tremendous power. Meanwhile, Red King appears before STORAGE. It seems, however, that this Red King has a secret...</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E96_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_171625.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922233000 +0800" stop="20230923000000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Z (EP12. The Cry of Life, 叫ぶ命, Sakebu Inochi)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ten years ago, a monster crashed to Earth and fell into a deep sleep. Now that monster, Grigio Raiden, has awakened! Z faces off against the monster, but something is wrong with Haruki... King Joe STORAGE Custom fights hard to follow the lackluster Z. How will this battle end?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E96_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_171625.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923000000 +0800" stop="20230923003000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Z (EP13. I'll Feast on Medals!, メダルいただきます!, Medaru Itadakimasu!)</title>
    <desc lang="en">With the sudden appearance of the Four-Dimensional Monster Bullton, the STORAGE base is thrown into chaos! Time and space become warped and twisted, transforming the STORAGE base into a dimensional prison. Meanwhile, Haruki is confronted with a mysterious phenomenon!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E96_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_171625.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923003000 +0800" stop="20230923010000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Z (EP14. Four-Dimensional Capriccio, 四次元狂騒曲, Yojigen Kyōsō-kyoku)</title>
    <desc lang="en">The space pirate, Alien Barossa sneaks into STORAGE to retrieve King Joe! This space pirate is known for using various robbed tools and weapons from space and is a powerful enemy! In addition, King Joe is about to move again! Can Haruki stop this pirate?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E96_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_171625.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923010000 +0800" stop="20230923031000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultra Galaxy Fight (The Destined Crossroad)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ultra Galaxy Fight: The Destined Crossroad is the third installment of the Ultra Galaxy Fight series, continued from the previous series Ultra Galaxy Fight: The Absolute Conspiracy which had a shocking ending. Ultra Heroes vs Absolutian, the destined battle is about to reshape the galaxy!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://news.ultramanconnection.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/62d70a2898f17d6b9a8422a6_ULTRA-GALAXY-FIGHT_-THE-DESTINED-CROSSROAD-TO-PREMIERE-ON-ULTRAMAN-CONNECTION.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923031000 +0800" stop="20230923033500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Trigger: New Generation Tiga (Ep24)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Today, GUTS-Select team was formed while Martian settlement Kengo Manaka lived his life as a botanist. Kengo has a fated encounter the giant of light from the past, and his name is Ultraman Trigger.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/ultra/images/b/bb/TriggerTitleCard.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20210617110145" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923033500 +0800" stop="20230923040000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Trigger: New Generation Tiga (Ep25)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Today, GUTS-Select team was formed while Martian settlement Kengo Manaka lived his life as a botanist. Kengo has a fated encounter the giant of light from the past, and his name is Ultraman Trigger.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/ultra/images/b/bb/TriggerTitleCard.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20210617110145" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923040000 +0800" stop="20230923043000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Trigger: New Generation Tiga (Ep01)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Today, GUTS-Select team was formed while Martian settlement Kengo Manaka lived his life as a botanist. Kengo has a fated encounter the giant of light from the past, and his name is Ultraman Trigger.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/ultra/images/b/bb/TriggerTitleCard.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20210617110145" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923043000 +0800" stop="20230923050000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Trigger: New Generation Tiga (Ep02)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Today, GUTS-Select team was formed while Martian settlement Kengo Manaka lived his life as a botanist. Kengo has a fated encounter the giant of light from the past, and his name is Ultraman Trigger.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/ultra/images/b/bb/TriggerTitleCard.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20210617110145" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923050000 +0800" stop="20230923053000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Trigger: New Generation Tiga (Ep03)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Today, GUTS-Select team was formed while Martian settlement Kengo Manaka lived his life as a botanist. Kengo has a fated encounter the giant of light from the past, and his name is Ultraman Trigger.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/ultra/images/b/bb/TriggerTitleCard.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20210617110145" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923053000 +0800" stop="20230923060000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Trigger: New Generation Tiga (Ep04)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Today, GUTS-Select team was formed while Martian settlement Kengo Manaka lived his life as a botanist. Kengo has a fated encounter the giant of light from the past, and his name is Ultraman Trigger.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/ultra/images/b/bb/TriggerTitleCard.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20210617110145" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923060000 +0800" stop="20230923063000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Z (EP10. Here Comes the Space Pirate! 宇宙海賊登場, Uchū Kaizoku Tōjō)</title>
    <desc lang="en">The space pirate, Alien Barossa sneaks into STORAGE to retrieve King Joe! This space pirate is known for using various robbed tools and weapons from space and is a powerful enemy! In addition, King Joe is about to move again! Can Haruki stop this pirate?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E96_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_171625.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923063000 +0800" stop="20230923070000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Z (EP11. What Must Be Defended, 守るべきもの, Mamorubeki mono)</title>
    <desc lang="en">SSA-3 King Joe STORAGE Custom is finally complete! With weapons equipped to every inch of its body, this super robot wields tremendous power. Meanwhile, Red King appears before STORAGE. It seems, however, that this Red King has a secret...</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E96_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_171625.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923070000 +0800" stop="20230923073000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Z (EP12. The Cry of Life, 叫ぶ命, Sakebu Inochi)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ten years ago, a monster crashed to Earth and fell into a deep sleep. Now that monster, Grigio Raiden, has awakened! Z faces off against the monster, but something is wrong with Haruki... King Joe STORAGE Custom fights hard to follow the lackluster Z. How will this battle end?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E96_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_171625.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923073000 +0800" stop="20230923080000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Z (EP13. I'll Feast on Medals!, メダルいただきます!, Medaru Itadakimasu!)</title>
    <desc lang="en">With the sudden appearance of the Four-Dimensional Monster Bullton, the STORAGE base is thrown into chaos! Time and space become warped and twisted, transforming the STORAGE base into a dimensional prison. Meanwhile, Haruki is confronted with a mysterious phenomenon!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E96_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_171625.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923080000 +0800" stop="20230923083000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Z (EP14. Four-Dimensional Capriccio, 四次元狂騒曲, Yojigen Kyōsō-kyoku)</title>
    <desc lang="en">The space pirate, Alien Barossa sneaks into STORAGE to retrieve King Joe! This space pirate is known for using various robbed tools and weapons from space and is a powerful enemy! In addition, King Joe is about to move again! Can Haruki stop this pirate?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E96_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_171625.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923083000 +0800" stop="20230923090000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Zero: The Chronicle (EP01)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ultraman Zero VS Darklops Zero - Part 1: Multidimensional Threat! (ウルトラマンゼロVSダークロプスゼロ パート①「多次元の脅威！」, Urutoraman Zero VS Dākuropusu Zero Pāto Wan - Tajigen no Kyōi!)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://resizer-acm.eco.astro.com.my/tr:w-800/https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E95_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_17255.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923090000 +0800" stop="20230923093000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Zero: The Chronicle (EP02)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ultraman Zero VS Darklops Zero - Part 2: Magic Bullet of Darkness (ウルトラマンゼロVSダークロプスゼロ パート②「暗黒の魔弾」, Urutoraman Zero VS Dākuropusu Zero Pāto Tsu - Ankoku no Madan)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://resizer-acm.eco.astro.com.my/tr:w-800/https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E95_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_17255.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923093000 +0800" stop="20230923100000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Zero: The Chronicle (EP03)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ultraman Zero VS Darklops Zero - Part 3: Big Bang of Flame (ウルトラマンゼロVSダークロプス ゼロ パート ③ 「炎のビッグバン!」, Urutoraman Zero VS Dākuropusu Zero Pāto Tsuri - Honō no Bigguban!)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://resizer-acm.eco.astro.com.my/tr:w-800/https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E95_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_17255.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923100000 +0800" stop="20230923103000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Zero: The Chronicle (EP04)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ultraman Zero THE MOVIE: Super Deciding Fight! The Belial Galactic Empire: Chapter of Bonds (ウルトラマンゼロ THE MOVIE 超決戦!ベリアル銀河帝国 絆の章, Urutoraman Zero THE MOVIE: Chōkessen! Beriaru Ginga Teikoku Kizuna no Shō)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://resizer-acm.eco.astro.com.my/tr:w-800/https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E95_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_17255.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923103000 +0800" stop="20230923110000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Zero: The Chronicle (EP05)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ultraman Zero THE MOVIE: Super Deciding Fight! The Belial Galactic Empire: Chapter of Flame (ウルトラマンゼロ THE MOVIE 超決戦!ベリアル銀河帝国 炎の章, Urutoraman Zero THE MOVIE: Chōkessen! Beriaru Ginga Teikoku Honō no Shō)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E95_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_17255.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923110000 +0800" stop="20230923113000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Zero: The Chronicle (EP06)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ultraman Zero THE MOVIE: Super Deciding Fight! The Belial Galactic Empire: Chapter of Mirrors (ウルトラマンゼロ THE MOVIE 超決戦!ベリアル銀河帝国 鏡の章, Urutoraman Zero THE MOVIE: Chōkessen! Beriaru Ginga Teikoku Kagami no Shō)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E95_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_17255.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923113000 +0800" stop="20230923120000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Zero: The Chronicle (EP07)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ultraman Zero THE MOVIE: Super Deciding Fight! The Belial Galactic Empire: Chapter of Steel (ウルトラマンゼロ THE MOVIE 超決戦!ベリアル銀河帝国 鋼の章, Urutoraman Zero THE MOVIE: Chōkessen! Beriaru Ginga Teikoku Hagane no Shō)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E95_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_17255.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923120000 +0800" stop="20230923131500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Trigger Episode Z</title>
    <desc lang="en">Two years have passed since the final battle and peace has been restored around the globe. However, things don't stay quiet for long when monsters once again begin to appear on Earth. At the same time, a series of mysterious break-ins take place at super ancient ruins around the world. Expert team GUTS-Select, led by a new captain, prepares the squad to launch an investigation. Little do they know, it is the beginning of a fierce battle with the fate of the universe in the balance. GUTS-Select and Ultraman Z rush into battle with our hero, Kengo Manaka, in the lead. A sinister figure emerges from the shadows: Evil Trigger, a sinister giant that inherits the shadow. To make everyone smile again, Ultraman Trigger and Haruki, human host of Ultraman Z, join forces with the new members of GUTS-Select as well as Ignis, human host of Trigger Dark, will take part in the ultimate battle between light and shadow!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_KDONB_IVP_LAND_672x378_20221115_223556.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923131500 +0800" stop="20230923134500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP17 Investigation from the Past 過去よりの調べ, Kako yori no Shirabe)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Captian Murahoshi is under investigation?! The Director of the TPU's Internal Affairs, Agent Nigel, suspects Captain and Agams might be working together. Kanata is shocked, but Nigel shows no mercy and looks for any suspicious acitivity from Murahoshi. Why doesn't Nigel trust Murahoshi? Is there any way to clear Captain's name?!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923134500 +0800" stop="20230923141500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP18 Invitation from Another Dimension 異次元からのいざない, I Jigen Kara no Izanai)</title>
    <desc lang="en">A sudden sinkhole appears in the city. Analysis shows it was caused by something beyond an average monster... Kanata, Ichika, and Ryumon head down to investigate where they encounter a mysterious shadow. Suddenly, Agams shows up again! Can Kanata keep his promise to save Agams?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923141500 +0800" stop="20230923144500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP19 Warriors on the Moon 月面の戦士たち, Getsumen no Senshi-tachi)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Kanata a.k.a. Ultraman Decker is thrown into another dimension by the extradimensional being Yapool! Just where in space has he been sent to? Kengo a.k.a. Ultraman Trigger comes to the rescue. Kanata and Kengo enjoy a moving reunion on the TPU's Lunar Base, but Yapool's evil reach isn't far behind...</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923144500 +0800" stop="20230923151500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP20 Lord Ragon らごんさま, Ragon-sama)</title>
    <desc lang="en">An incident of an attacking from an unidentified monster takes place in a modern city, built where it which was once an ocean, Wadatsumi City!! Kaizaki and Ichika are immediately sent to investigate. The pair find a suspicious old woman, a mysterious girl, a crowd wearing peculiar masks, and a strange green creature. Is this a place where myterious events gather?!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923151500 +0800" stop="20230923154500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP21 The Price of Prosperity 繁栄の代償, Han'ei no Daishō)</title>
    <desc lang="en">The S-Plasma fusion reactor is a new technology in development. The tremendous energy it could produce has the potential to allow humanity to reach the speed of light. However, this unknown energy source is concealed as a secret... Monsters are born, Agams' shadow squirms, and a truth is revealed. How will Kanata react to this crisis?!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923154500 +0800" stop="20230923161500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP22 The Fall of Bazdo 衰亡のバズド, Suibō no Bazudo)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Fugitive Agams suddenly reaches out to GUTS-Select and Captain Murahoshi is called to Agams’ hideout alone… Finally, Agams reveals the truth of the shocking events from the future timeline?! What does he mean by “Earthlings’ crime”? Can Kanata and GUTS-Select finally take Agams into custody?!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923161500 +0800" stop="20230923164500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP23 The Sky of Despair 絶望の空, Zetsubō no Sora)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Agams is an entirely different person after his fight with Decker. Kanata searches how to save Agams from himself, meeting with the captured fugitive. They have a peaceful talk for the first time in a while gives Kanata a glimpse of Agams’ true feelings… But suddenly Sphere attacks, ruining the moment, and then an ominous, great shadow appears?!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923164500 +0800" stop="20230923171500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP24 End of a Dream 夢の果て, Yume no Hate)</title>
    <desc lang="en">3 hours left until the Sphere Barrier starts to shrink. The 3 hours is the last hours of hope for humanity! To destory the Sphere Oblelisks, Kanata and GUTS-Select start a joint operation with TPU. However, the Terraphaser stands before them...! What will Kanata do to save Agams!?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923171500 +0800" stop="20230923174500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP25 The Light Far Beyond 彼方の光, Kanata no Hikari)</title>
    <desc lang="en">As Earth's apocalypse approaches, the injured GUTS-Select members puts their final plan into action in hopes to defeat Mother Spheresaurus! Will Kanata and the others be able to move forward to the future!? And what awaits them there!?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923174500 +0800" stop="20230923181500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Z (EP10. Here Comes the Space Pirate! 宇宙海賊登場, Uchū Kaizoku Tōjō)</title>
    <desc lang="en">The space pirate, Alien Barossa sneaks into STORAGE to retrieve King Joe! This space pirate is known for using various robbed tools and weapons from space and is a powerful enemy! In addition, King Joe is about to move again! Can Haruki stop this pirate?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E96_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_171625.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923181500 +0800" stop="20230923184500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Z (EP11. What Must Be Defended, 守るべきもの, Mamorubeki mono)</title>
    <desc lang="en">SSA-3 King Joe STORAGE Custom is finally complete! With weapons equipped to every inch of its body, this super robot wields tremendous power. Meanwhile, Red King appears before STORAGE. It seems, however, that this Red King has a secret...</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E96_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_171625.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923184500 +0800" stop="20230923191500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Z (EP12. The Cry of Life, 叫ぶ命, Sakebu Inochi)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ten years ago, a monster crashed to Earth and fell into a deep sleep. Now that monster, Grigio Raiden, has awakened! Z faces off against the monster, but something is wrong with Haruki... King Joe STORAGE Custom fights hard to follow the lackluster Z. How will this battle end?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E96_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_171625.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923191500 +0800" stop="20230923194500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Z (EP13. I'll Feast on Medals!, メダルいただきます!, Medaru Itadakimasu!)</title>
    <desc lang="en">With the sudden appearance of the Four-Dimensional Monster Bullton, the STORAGE base is thrown into chaos! Time and space become warped and twisted, transforming the STORAGE base into a dimensional prison. Meanwhile, Haruki is confronted with a mysterious phenomenon!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E96_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_171625.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923194500 +0800" stop="20230923201500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Z (EP14. Four-Dimensional Capriccio, 四次元狂騒曲, Yojigen Kyōsō-kyoku)</title>
    <desc lang="en">The space pirate, Alien Barossa sneaks into STORAGE to retrieve King Joe! This space pirate is known for using various robbed tools and weapons from space and is a powerful enemy! In addition, King Joe is about to move again! Can Haruki stop this pirate?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E96_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_171625.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923201500 +0800" stop="20230923204500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Z (EP15. A Warrior's Duty, 戦士の使命, Senshi no Shimei)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Emergency contact from Ultraman Geed! It seems that a distortion is created in the universe, and a void monster, Greeza, who returns everything to nothing, appears. We need new power to face this threat! Yes, the strongest figure of Ultraman Z is born here now!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E96_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_171625.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923204500 +0800" stop="20230923220000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Trigger Episode Z</title>
    <desc lang="en">Two years have passed since the final battle and peace has been restored around the globe. However, things don't stay quiet for long when monsters once again begin to appear on Earth. At the same time, a series of mysterious break-ins take place at super ancient ruins around the world. Expert team GUTS-Select, led by a new captain, prepares the squad to launch an investigation. Little do they know, it is the beginning of a fierce battle with the fate of the universe in the balance. GUTS-Select and Ultraman Z rush into battle with our hero, Kengo Manaka, in the lead. A sinister figure emerges from the shadows: Evil Trigger, a sinister giant that inherits the shadow. To make everyone smile again, Ultraman Trigger and Haruki, human host of Ultraman Z, join forces with the new members of GUTS-Select as well as Ignis, human host of Trigger Dark, will take part in the ultimate battle between light and shadow!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_KDONB_IVP_LAND_672x378_20221115_223556.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923220000 +0800" stop="20230923223000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Zero: The Chronicle (EP01)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ultraman Zero VS Darklops Zero - Part 1: Multidimensional Threat! (ウルトラマンゼロVSダークロプスゼロ パート①「多次元の脅威！」, Urutoraman Zero VS Dākuropusu Zero Pāto Wan - Tajigen no Kyōi!)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://resizer-acm.eco.astro.com.my/tr:w-800/https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E95_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_17255.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923223000 +0800" stop="20230923230000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Zero: The Chronicle (EP02)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ultraman Zero VS Darklops Zero - Part 2: Magic Bullet of Darkness (ウルトラマンゼロVSダークロプスゼロ パート②「暗黒の魔弾」, Urutoraman Zero VS Dākuropusu Zero Pāto Tsu - Ankoku no Madan)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://resizer-acm.eco.astro.com.my/tr:w-800/https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E95_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_17255.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923230000 +0800" stop="20230923233000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Zero: The Chronicle (EP03)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ultraman Zero VS Darklops Zero - Part 3: Big Bang of Flame (ウルトラマンゼロVSダークロプス ゼロ パート ③ 「炎のビッグバン!」, Urutoraman Zero VS Dākuropusu Zero Pāto Tsuri - Honō no Bigguban!)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://resizer-acm.eco.astro.com.my/tr:w-800/https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E95_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_17255.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230923233000 +0800" stop="20230924000000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Zero: The Chronicle (EP04)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ultraman Zero THE MOVIE: Super Deciding Fight! The Belial Galactic Empire: Chapter of Bonds (ウルトラマンゼロ THE MOVIE 超決戦!ベリアル銀河帝国 絆の章, Urutoraman Zero THE MOVIE: Chōkessen! Beriaru Ginga Teikoku Kizuna no Shō)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://resizer-acm.eco.astro.com.my/tr:w-800/https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E95_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_17255.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924000000 +0800" stop="20230924003000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Zero: The Chronicle (EP05)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ultraman Zero THE MOVIE: Super Deciding Fight! The Belial Galactic Empire: Chapter of Flame (ウルトラマンゼロ THE MOVIE 超決戦!ベリアル銀河帝国 炎の章, Urutoraman Zero THE MOVIE: Chōkessen! Beriaru Ginga Teikoku Honō no Shō)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E95_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_17255.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924003000 +0800" stop="20230924010000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Zero: The Chronicle (EP06)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Ultraman Zero THE MOVIE: Super Deciding Fight! The Belial Galactic Empire: Chapter of Mirrors (ウルトラマンゼロ THE MOVIE 超決戦!ベリアル銀河帝国 鏡の章, Urutoraman Zero THE MOVIE: Chōkessen! Beriaru Ginga Teikoku Kagami no Shō)</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_51E95_IVP_LAND_672x378_2022126_17255.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924010000 +0800" stop="20230924021500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Trigger Episode Z</title>
    <desc lang="en">Two years have passed since the final battle and peace has been restored around the globe. However, things don't stay quiet for long when monsters once again begin to appear on Earth. At the same time, a series of mysterious break-ins take place at super ancient ruins around the world. Expert team GUTS-Select, led by a new captain, prepares the squad to launch an investigation. Little do they know, it is the beginning of a fierce battle with the fate of the universe in the balance. GUTS-Select and Ultraman Z rush into battle with our hero, Kengo Manaka, in the lead. A sinister figure emerges from the shadows: Evil Trigger, a sinister giant that inherits the shadow. To make everyone smile again, Ultraman Trigger and Haruki, human host of Ultraman Z, join forces with the new members of GUTS-Select as well as Ignis, human host of Trigger Dark, will take part in the ultimate battle between light and shadow!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_KDONB_IVP_LAND_672x378_20221115_223556.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924021500 +0800" stop="20230924024000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP17 Investigation from the Past 過去よりの調べ, Kako yori no Shirabe)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Captian Murahoshi is under investigation?! The Director of the TPU's Internal Affairs, Agent Nigel, suspects Captain and Agams might be working together. Kanata is shocked, but Nigel shows no mercy and looks for any suspicious acitivity from Murahoshi. Why doesn't Nigel trust Murahoshi? Is there any way to clear Captain's name?!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924024000 +0800" stop="20230924030500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP18 Invitation from Another Dimension 異次元からのいざない, I Jigen Kara no Izanai)</title>
    <desc lang="en">A sudden sinkhole appears in the city. Analysis shows it was caused by something beyond an average monster... Kanata, Ichika, and Ryumon head down to investigate where they encounter a mysterious shadow. Suddenly, Agams shows up again! Can Kanata keep his promise to save Agams?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924030500 +0800" stop="20230924033000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP19 Warriors on the Moon 月面の戦士たち, Getsumen no Senshi-tachi)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Kanata a.k.a. Ultraman Decker is thrown into another dimension by the extradimensional being Yapool! Just where in space has he been sent to? Kengo a.k.a. Ultraman Trigger comes to the rescue. Kanata and Kengo enjoy a moving reunion on the TPU's Lunar Base, but Yapool's evil reach isn't far behind...</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924033000 +0800" stop="20230924035500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP20 Lord Ragon らごんさま, Ragon-sama)</title>
    <desc lang="en">An incident of an attacking from an unidentified monster takes place in a modern city, built where it which was once an ocean, Wadatsumi City!! Kaizaki and Ichika are immediately sent to investigate. The pair find a suspicious old woman, a mysterious girl, a crowd wearing peculiar masks, and a strange green creature. Is this a place where myterious events gather?!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924035500 +0800" stop="20230924042000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP21 The Price of Prosperity 繁栄の代償, Han'ei no Daishō)</title>
    <desc lang="en">The S-Plasma fusion reactor is a new technology in development. The tremendous energy it could produce has the potential to allow humanity to reach the speed of light. However, this unknown energy source is concealed as a secret... Monsters are born, Agams' shadow squirms, and a truth is revealed. How will Kanata react to this crisis?!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924042000 +0800" stop="20230924044500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP22 The Fall of Bazdo 衰亡のバズド, Suibō no Bazudo)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Fugitive Agams suddenly reaches out to GUTS-Select and Captain Murahoshi is called to Agams’ hideout alone… Finally, Agams reveals the truth of the shocking events from the future timeline?! What does he mean by “Earthlings’ crime”? Can Kanata and GUTS-Select finally take Agams into custody?!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924044500 +0800" stop="20230924060000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Trigger Episode Z</title>
    <desc lang="en">Two years have passed since the final battle and peace has been restored around the globe. However, things don't stay quiet for long when monsters once again begin to appear on Earth. At the same time, a series of mysterious break-ins take place at super ancient ruins around the world. Expert team GUTS-Select, led by a new captain, prepares the squad to launch an investigation. Little do they know, it is the beginning of a fierce battle with the fate of the universe in the balance. GUTS-Select and Ultraman Z rush into battle with our hero, Kengo Manaka, in the lead. A sinister figure emerges from the shadows: Evil Trigger, a sinister giant that inherits the shadow. To make everyone smile again, Ultraman Trigger and Haruki, human host of Ultraman Z, join forces with the new members of GUTS-Select as well as Ignis, human host of Trigger Dark, will take part in the ultimate battle between light and shadow!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_KDONB_IVP_LAND_672x378_20221115_223556.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924060000 +0800" stop="20230924063000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Blazar (EP07 Rainbow Appears: Part 1 虹が出た（前編）, Niji ga Deta (Zenpen))</title>
    <desc lang="en">Upside-down rainbows are being sighted throughout Japan. They are said to herald the onset of rain. Gento suspects that a kaiju may be behind this and decides to visit Professor Yokomine, a leading kaijuologist and also his mentor from school. Yokomine tells him about Nijikagachi, a god-like being that can at times bless the land with rain and at times summon utter destruction. That's when Gento receives news about an appearance of a giant kaiju!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_KIFXH_IVP_LAND_672x378_2023616_151457.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924063000 +0800" stop="20230924070000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Blazar (EP08 Rainbow Appears: Part 2 虹が出た（後編）, Niji ga deta (Kōhen))</title>
    <desc lang="en">The typhoons that Nijikagachi created are about to wash away civilization. Gento decides to deploy Earth Garon's new Mod.2 unit into battle to defeat Nijikagachi. Teruaki, who had a deep respect for Yokomine, goes to persuade the mastermind of the plot.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_KIFXH_IVP_LAND_672x378_2023616_151457.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924070000 +0800" stop="20230924073000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Blazar (EP09 Planet of Music オトノホシ, Otonohoshi)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Anri receives a letter. It contained a concert ticket for a band led by Hoichi Tsukushi, someone that Anri had gotten to know through music. That's when the robot kaiju Garamon appears from a meteorite that came from outer space. Anri realizes that Garamon's behavior is controlled by a mysterious sound wave, and she has a hunch...</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_KIFXH_IVP_LAND_672x378_2023616_151457.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924073000 +0800" stop="20230924080000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Blazar (EP10 Parent and Child 親と子, Oya to Ko)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Gento's son, Jun, wants to go see a newly discovered egg shown on television, so the Hiruma family decide to go on a day trip to visit it. There, they witness the birth of Baby Demaaga. In the midst of the capture operation led by the GGF, the mother Demaaga makes an appearance. The GGF launches attacks as the parent kaiju approaches its baby. While evacuating, Gento can't help but feel mixed emotions seeing Demaaga trying to protect its child. Suddenly, the Blazar Brace appears on Gento's left arm.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_KIFXH_IVP_LAND_672x378_2023616_151457.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924080000 +0800" stop="20230924083000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Blazar (EP11 Escape)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Following the battle with Demaaga, Gento can not hide his confusion about the alien being that resides in his own body. That's when a meteorite flies in from outer space. It lands on Earth, evading the GGF's attempts to intercept it, and transforms into the kaiju Gebalga. It seemed that Earth Garon would have the upper hand in the fight until Gebalga revealed it's surprising ability...</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_KIFXH_IVP_LAND_672x378_2023616_151457.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924083000 +0800" stop="20230924090000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP25 The Light Far Beyond 彼方の光, Kanata no Hikari)</title>
    <desc lang="en">As Earth's apocalypse approaches, the injured GUTS-Select members puts their final plan into action in hopes to defeat Mother Spheresaurus! Will Kanata and the others be able to move forward to the future!? And what awaits them there!?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924090000 +0800" stop="20230924093000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP01 Day of the Attack (襲来の日, Shūrai no hi)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Several years after the world was saved by Ultraman Trigger, mankind has turned its gaze skywards to space. Suddenly, unidentified orbs dubbed “Sphere” invade! They begin their attack on Earth. Asumi Kanata, son of a rice cracker grocer, witnesses this tragedy unfold before him, and vows to protect the people. As he does, he is enveloped in light! And the new form he takes on... Is it a new Ultraman?!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924093000 +0800" stop="20230924100000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP02 Kanata's Resolve 決意のカナタ, Ketsui no Kanata)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Kanata enters the TPU training school, and begins marching drills with classmates Ichika and Ryumon. However, he and Ryumon start butting heads after a difference in opinion... Just then, Deathdrago appears before them! Will Kanata pull through this deadly situation? And can the three of them become members of GUTS-Select?!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924100000 +0800" stop="20230924103000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP03 Move Out, GUTS-Select! 出動! GUTS-Select, Shutsudō! Gattsu Serekuto)</title>
    <desc lang="en">A new aircraft GUTS Hawk deploys to GUTS-Select. To fully utilize its power, GUTS-Select need to coordinate with the Hawk's AI pilot, HANE2! But communicating with HANE2 proves a difficult task for Kanata and his team mates …. The sudden appearance of Gomora only adds to their difficulties. Don't give up, Decker! Use your new power to save the day!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924103000 +0800" stop="20230924110000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP04 The Destructive Monster Awakens 破壊獣覚醒, Hakaijū Kakusei)</title>
    <desc lang="en">A mysterious giant capsule suddenly appears in a forgotten onsen (hot spring) town! Although, the mayor is taking pictures and looks oddly happy? Mons-Ahgar appears to throw GUTS-Select and the town further into chaos! Their hopes to save the day lie in promising new technology, and so Kanata and crew turn their efforts into combining the two GUTS aircrafts into one: the GUTS Gryphon!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924110000 +0800" stop="20230924113000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP05 Glutton of the Lake 湖の食いしん坊, Mizu'umi no Kuishinbō)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Eleking suddenly appeared in the city! Ichika meets a mysterious girl named Yuko at the scene. Recently, Eleking has been stealing and eating electricity, but is there any connection between the two? In addition, there is something strange with Ichika's encounter with Yuko. Where will her straight forward feelings lead her?!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924113000 +0800" stop="20230924120000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP06 Subterranean Monster Appears! And Appears! 地底怪獣現わる! 現わる!, Chitei Kaijū Arawaru! Arawaru!)</title>
    <desc lang="en">A sazame bamboo flower, a harbinger of disaster blooms. A golden rainbow appears in the sky and a subterranean monster emerges. Ryumon is injured in this unprecedented situation. Kanata tries to cheer him up, but... What is Ryumon staring at?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924120000 +0800" stop="20230924131500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker Finale (Journey to Beyond)</title>
    <desc lang="en">A peculiar sound echoes through the sky. Those who hear it faint, and eventually vanish. Expert team GUTS-Select investigate but are met with attacks from an alien army and a pitch black mobile fortress, Zorgaus, piloted by Professor Gibellus who seeks to rule the skies of Earth. As Kanata and crew find themselves in trouble, a mysterious woman who knows Gibellus suddenly appears. The woman, Dinas, possesses a mysterious power. With her “duty to protect,” Dinas and GUTS-Select work together to foil the evil scheme, but a barbaric “Emperor Beast” appears and casts a shadow over the events. Kanata, Dinas, and GUTS-Select begin an all-out battle to decide the fate of the Earth and entire galaxy!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/_2hG3hdpg7c/maxresdefault.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924131500 +0800" stop="20230924134500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Trigger: New Generation Tiga (Ep04)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Today, GUTS-Select team was formed while Martian settlement Kengo Manaka lived his life as a botanist. Kengo has a fated encounter the giant of light from the past, and his name is Ultraman Trigger.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/ultra/images/b/bb/TriggerTitleCard.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20210617110145" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924134500 +0800" stop="20230924141500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Trigger: New Generation Tiga (Ep05)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Today, GUTS-Select team was formed while Martian settlement Kengo Manaka lived his life as a botanist. Kengo has a fated encounter the giant of light from the past, and his name is Ultraman Trigger.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/ultra/images/b/bb/TriggerTitleCard.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20210617110145" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924141500 +0800" stop="20230924144500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Trigger: New Generation Tiga (Ep06)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Today, GUTS-Select team was formed while Martian settlement Kengo Manaka lived his life as a botanist. Kengo has a fated encounter the giant of light from the past, and his name is Ultraman Trigger.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/ultra/images/b/bb/TriggerTitleCard.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20210617110145" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924144500 +0800" stop="20230924151500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Trigger: New Generation Tiga (Ep07)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Today, GUTS-Select team was formed while Martian settlement Kengo Manaka lived his life as a botanist. Kengo has a fated encounter the giant of light from the past, and his name is Ultraman Trigger.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/ultra/images/b/bb/TriggerTitleCard.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20210617110145" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924151500 +0800" stop="20230924154500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Trigger: New Generation Tiga (Ep08)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Today, GUTS-Select team was formed while Martian settlement Kengo Manaka lived his life as a botanist. Kengo has a fated encounter the giant of light from the past, and his name is Ultraman Trigger.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/ultra/images/b/bb/TriggerTitleCard.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20210617110145" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924154500 +0800" stop="20230924161500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Trigger: New Generation Tiga (Ep09)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Today, GUTS-Select team was formed while Martian settlement Kengo Manaka lived his life as a botanist. Kengo has a fated encounter the giant of light from the past, and his name is Ultraman Trigger.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/ultra/images/b/bb/TriggerTitleCard.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20210617110145" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924161500 +0800" stop="20230924164500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Trigger: New Generation Tiga (Ep10)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Today, GUTS-Select team was formed while Martian settlement Kengo Manaka lived his life as a botanist. Kengo has a fated encounter the giant of light from the past, and his name is Ultraman Trigger.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/ultra/images/b/bb/TriggerTitleCard.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20210617110145" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924164500 +0800" stop="20230924171500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Trigger: New Generation Tiga (Ep11)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Today, GUTS-Select team was formed while Martian settlement Kengo Manaka lived his life as a botanist. Kengo has a fated encounter the giant of light from the past, and his name is Ultraman Trigger.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/ultra/images/b/bb/TriggerTitleCard.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20210617110145" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924171500 +0800" stop="20230924174500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Trigger: New Generation Tiga (Ep12)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Today, GUTS-Select team was formed while Martian settlement Kengo Manaka lived his life as a botanist. Kengo has a fated encounter the giant of light from the past, and his name is Ultraman Trigger.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/ultra/images/b/bb/TriggerTitleCard.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20210617110145" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924174500 +0800" stop="20230924181500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Blazar (EP07 Rainbow Appears: Part 1 虹が出た（前編）, Niji ga Deta (Zenpen))</title>
    <desc lang="en">Upside-down rainbows are being sighted throughout Japan. They are said to herald the onset of rain. Gento suspects that a kaiju may be behind this and decides to visit Professor Yokomine, a leading kaijuologist and also his mentor from school. Yokomine tells him about Nijikagachi, a god-like being that can at times bless the land with rain and at times summon utter destruction. That's when Gento receives news about an appearance of a giant kaiju!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_KIFXH_IVP_LAND_672x378_2023616_151457.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924181500 +0800" stop="20230924184500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Blazar (EP08 Rainbow Appears: Part 2 虹が出た（後編）, Niji ga deta (Kōhen))</title>
    <desc lang="en">The typhoons that Nijikagachi created are about to wash away civilization. Gento decides to deploy Earth Garon's new Mod.2 unit into battle to defeat Nijikagachi. Teruaki, who had a deep respect for Yokomine, goes to persuade the mastermind of the plot.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_KIFXH_IVP_LAND_672x378_2023616_151457.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924184500 +0800" stop="20230924191500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Blazar (EP09 Planet of Music オトノホシ, Otonohoshi)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Anri receives a letter. It contained a concert ticket for a band led by Hoichi Tsukushi, someone that Anri had gotten to know through music. That's when the robot kaiju Garamon appears from a meteorite that came from outer space. Anri realizes that Garamon's behavior is controlled by a mysterious sound wave, and she has a hunch...</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_KIFXH_IVP_LAND_672x378_2023616_151457.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924191500 +0800" stop="20230924194500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Blazar (EP10 Parent and Child 親と子, Oya to Ko)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Gento's son, Jun, wants to go see a newly discovered egg shown on television, so the Hiruma family decide to go on a day trip to visit it. There, they witness the birth of Baby Demaaga. In the midst of the capture operation led by the GGF, the mother Demaaga makes an appearance. The GGF launches attacks as the parent kaiju approaches its baby. While evacuating, Gento can't help but feel mixed emotions seeing Demaaga trying to protect its child. Suddenly, the Blazar Brace appears on Gento's left arm.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_KIFXH_IVP_LAND_672x378_2023616_151457.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924194500 +0800" stop="20230924201500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Blazar (EP11 Escape)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Following the battle with Demaaga, Gento can not hide his confusion about the alien being that resides in his own body. That's when a meteorite flies in from outer space. It lands on Earth, evading the GGF's attempts to intercept it, and transforms into the kaiju Gebalga. It seemed that Earth Garon would have the upper hand in the fight until Gebalga revealed it's surprising ability...</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_KIFXH_IVP_LAND_672x378_2023616_151457.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924201500 +0800" stop="20230924204500 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Blazar (EP07 Rainbow Appears: Part 1 虹が出た（前編）, Niji ga Deta (Zenpen))</title>
    <desc lang="en">Upside-down rainbows are being sighted throughout Japan. They are said to herald the onset of rain. Gento suspects that a kaiju may be behind this and decides to visit Professor Yokomine, a leading kaijuologist and also his mentor from school. Yokomine tells him about Nijikagachi, a god-like being that can at times bless the land with rain and at times summon utter destruction. That's when Gento receives news about an appearance of a giant kaiju!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://s3-ap-southeast-1.amazonaws.com/ams-astro/production/IVPVodImages/IVP(STB_OTT_STV)_KIFXH_IVP_LAND_672x378_2023616_151457.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924204500 +0800" stop="20230924220000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker Finale (Journey to Beyond)</title>
    <desc lang="en">A peculiar sound echoes through the sky. Those who hear it faint, and eventually vanish. Expert team GUTS-Select investigate but are met with attacks from an alien army and a pitch black mobile fortress, Zorgaus, piloted by Professor Gibellus who seeks to rule the skies of Earth. As Kanata and crew find themselves in trouble, a mysterious woman who knows Gibellus suddenly appears. The woman, Dinas, possesses a mysterious power. With her “duty to protect,” Dinas and GUTS-Select work together to foil the evil scheme, but a barbaric “Emperor Beast” appears and casts a shadow over the events. Kanata, Dinas, and GUTS-Select begin an all-out battle to decide the fate of the Earth and entire galaxy!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/_2hG3hdpg7c/maxresdefault.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924220000 +0800" stop="20230924223000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP25 The Light Far Beyond 彼方の光, Kanata no Hikari)</title>
    <desc lang="en">As Earth's apocalypse approaches, the injured GUTS-Select members puts their final plan into action in hopes to defeat Mother Spheresaurus! Will Kanata and the others be able to move forward to the future!? And what awaits them there!?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924223000 +0800" stop="20230924230000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP01 Day of the Attack (襲来の日, Shūrai no hi)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Several years after the world was saved by Ultraman Trigger, mankind has turned its gaze skywards to space. Suddenly, unidentified orbs dubbed “Sphere” invade! They begin their attack on Earth. Asumi Kanata, son of a rice cracker grocer, witnesses this tragedy unfold before him, and vows to protect the people. As he does, he is enveloped in light! And the new form he takes on... Is it a new Ultraman?!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924230000 +0800" stop="20230924233000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP02 Kanata's Resolve 決意のカナタ, Ketsui no Kanata)</title>
    <desc lang="en">Kanata enters the TPU training school, and begins marching drills with classmates Ichika and Ryumon. However, he and Ryumon start butting heads after a difference in opinion... Just then, Deathdrago appears before them! Will Kanata pull through this deadly situation? And can the three of them become members of GUTS-Select?!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230924233000 +0800" stop="20230925000000 +0800" channel="AS400">
    <title lang="en">Ultraman Decker (EP03 Move Out, GUTS-Select! 出動! GUTS-Select, Shutsudō! Gattsu Serekuto)</title>
    <desc lang="en">A new aircraft GUTS Hawk deploys to GUTS-Select. To fully utilize its power, GUTS-Select need to coordinate with the Hawk's AI pilot, HANE2! But communicating with HANE2 proves a difficult task for Kanata and his team mates …. The sudden appearance of Gomora only adds to their difficulties. Don't give up, Decker! Use your new power to save the day!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Ultraman</category>
    <icon src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FhAMvQXaUAAa5tf?format=jpg&name=large" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921000000 +0800" stop="20230921003500 +0800" channel="AS825">
    <title lang="en">BEIN SPORTS 4</title>
    <desc lang="en">Catch the broadcast of UEFA Champion's League 2023/2024, Match Day 1 on 20th September and 21st September 2023.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Football</category>
    <icon src="https://img.uefa.com/imgml/uefacom/ucl/social/og-default.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921003500 +0800" stop="20230921025000 +0800" channel="AS825">
    <title lang="en">(L) UCL: Galatasaray v Copenhagen</title>
    <desc lang="en">LIVE: UEFA Champions League 2023/24: Match Day 1: Galatasaray v FC Copenhagen, from Ali Sami SYen Spor Kompleksi, Istanbul, Türkiye.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Football</category>
    <icon src="https://img.uefa.com/imgml/uefacom/ucl/social/og-default.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921025000 +0800" stop="20230921051500 +0800" channel="AS825">
    <title lang="en">(L) UCL: Arsenal v PSV</title>
    <desc lang="en">LIVE: UEFA Champions League 2023/24: Match Day 1: Arsenal vs PSV Eindhoven, from Arsenal Stadium, London.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Football</category>
    <icon src="https://img.uefa.com/imgml/uefacom/ucl/social/og-default.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921051500 +0800" stop="20230921060000 +0800" channel="AS825">
    <title lang="en">BEIN SPORTS 4</title>
    <desc lang="en">Catch the broadcast of UEFA Champion's League 2023/2024, Match Day 1 on 20th September and 21st September 2023.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Football</category>
    <icon src="https://img.uefa.com/imgml/uefacom/ucl/social/og-default.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921060000 +0800" stop="20230921120000 +0800" channel="AS825">
    <title lang="en">BEIN SPORTS 4</title>
    <desc lang="en">Catch the broadcast of UEFA Europa League 2023/2024, Match Day 1.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Football</category>
    <icon src="https://img.uefa.com/imgml/uefacom/uel/social/og-default.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921120000 +0800" stop="20230921180000 +0800" channel="AS825">
    <title lang="en">BEIN SPORTS 4</title>
    <desc lang="en">Catch the broadcast of UEFA Europa League 2023/2024, Match Day 1.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Football</category>
    <icon src="https://img.uefa.com/imgml/uefacom/uel/social/og-default.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230921180000 +0800" stop="20230922000000 +0800" channel="AS825">
    <title lang="en">BEIN SPORTS 4</title>
    <desc lang="en">Catch the broadcast of UEFA Europa League 2023/2024, Match Day 1.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Football</category>
    <icon src="https://img.uefa.com/imgml/uefacom/uel/social/og-default.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922000000 +0800" stop="20230922003500 +0800" channel="AS825">
    <title lang="en">BEIN SPORTS 4</title>
    <desc lang="en">Catch the broadcast of UEFA Europa League 2023/2024, Match Day 1.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Football</category>
    <icon src="https://img.uefa.com/imgml/uefacom/uel/social/og-default.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922003500 +0800" stop="20230922025000 +0800" channel="AS825">
    <title lang="en">(L) UEL: Rennes vs Maccabi Haifa</title>
    <desc lang="en">LIVE: UEFA Europa League 2023/24: Match Day 1: Rennes vs Maccabi Haifa.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Football</category>
    <icon src="https://thumbor.prod.vidiocdn.com/0qv9VWqirpotap5f7cgLaX2HwDA=/784x441/filters:quality(70)/vidio-web-prod-livestreaming/uploads/livestreaming/cover/15022/uefa-europa-league-cover-8462e6.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922025000 +0800" stop="20230922051500 +0800" channel="AS825">
    <title lang="en">(L) UEL: Ajax vs Marseille</title>
    <desc lang="en">LIVE: UEFA Europa League 2023/24: Match Day 1: Ajax vs Marseille.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Football</category>
    <icon src="https://english.ajax.nl/media/h2ihdtnp/ticketshop-wedstrijden-16x9-ajax-marseille.png" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
<programme start="20230922051500 +0800" stop="20230922060000 +0800" channel="AS825">
    <title lang="en">BEIN SPORTS 4</title>
    <desc lang="en">Catch the broadcast of UEFA Europa League 2023/2024, Match Day 1.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Football</category>
    <icon src="https://img.uefa.com/imgml/uefacom/uel/social/og-default.jpg" />
    <rating system="MY">
      <value>U</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
</tv>